A Guide to the Papers of Harry Walter Roberts 1921,1970
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Correspondence, Family, Personal, and Community Activities
  - Personal
    - Correspondence-Personal October, 1966 (Box-folder 12:15)
    - Correspondence-Personal November, 1966 (Box-folder 12:16)
    - Correspondence-Personal December, 1966 (Box-folder 12:17)
  - Community Activities
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence January-August, 1943 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence September-December, 1943 (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence January-May, 1944 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence June-December, 1944 (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 13:8)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence January-September, 1946 (Box-folder 13:9)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence October-December, 1946 (Box-folder 13:10)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence January-December, 1947 (Box-folder 13:11)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence March-July, 1949 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence August-December, 1949 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence January-April, 1950 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence May-September, 1950 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence February-August, 1951 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence September-October 1951 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 14:8)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1956-1961 (Box-folder 14:9)
    - Community Activities-Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 14:10)
    - The Laundry Workers Union-Correspondence 1940 (Box-folder 14:11)
    - The Ordell Waller Case-Correspondence 1941-1942 (Box-folder 14:12)
    - Petition of Error (Walker)-Correspondence (Box-folder 14:13)
    - Walker (News Clippings) 1942 (Box-folder 14:14)
    - Conference Tennessee: Negro Rural Life Leader 1940 (Box-folder 14:15)
- Organizations and Affiliations
  - The Association of Social Science Teachers in Negro Schools
    - Constitution 1937 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Minutes May 3-4, 1956 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - Reports (Secretary and Treasurer) 1939 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - Activities Reports 1939 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - Fifth Conference March 23-April 13, 1940 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Reports 1938-1942 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Reports: Roberts 1957 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Annual Reports 1959-1961 (Box-folder 15:8)
    - Annual Meeting Minutes 1954 (Box-folder 15:9)
    - May Meeting: Houston Texas 1957 (Box-folder 15:10)
    - Annual Meeting 1959 (Box-folder 15:11)
    - Honor Society Members 1961 (Box-folder 15:12)
    - Regional Director-Correspondence 1953-1954 (Box-folder 15:13)
    - Regional Director: Roberts 1954 (Box-folder 15:14)
    - Members-Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 15:15)
    - Members-Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 15:16)
    - S.V.P. Correspondence March-April, 1955 (Box-folder 15:17)
    - Membership-Correspondence January-February, 1955 (Box-folder 15:18)
    - Membership-Correspondence 1954, 1956 (Box-folder 15:19)
    - Member's List 1956 (Box-folder 15:20)
    - Member Directory (Box-folder 15:21)
    - Correspondence Member Schools 1954 (Box-folder 15:22)
    - Member List (schools/individuals) 1955 (Box-folder 15:23)
    - Directors List 1955 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Journal of Science Techers-Correspondence 1956, 1960 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Social Science Teachers-Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Roberts-Louise S. Hamilton- Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Roberts-Miller (Sec.)-Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Roberts-Miller-Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - Roberts-Miller-Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Miller-Correspondence 1958-1959 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - First Vice President Program Chair 1955 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Roberts-Chick F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:10)
    - Roberts-Riden F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Roberts-Savage F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:12)
    - Roberts-Smith F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:13)
    - Roberts-McIntosh F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:14)
    - Roberts-C.E. Teller F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:15)
    - Roberts-Gaines F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:16)
    - Roberts-E.S Richardson-F.V.P-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 16:17)
    - Program Chair F.V.P-Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder 16:18)
    - Roberts-Smith F.V.P-Correspondence 1956-1962 (Box-folder 16:19)
    - Roberts-Johnson F.V.P-Correspondence 1956-1962 (Box-folder 16:20)
    - Roberts-Latimer-Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 16:21)
    - Correspondence 1939-1942 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Correspondence 1945-1947 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Promotion-General 1955-1957 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - General Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - General Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - General Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - The Montgomery Advertiser and The Alabama Journal 1960 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Correspondence The Montgomery Advertiser and The Alabama Journal 1960 (Box-folder 17:8)
    - Correspondence The New Statesman and the Nation 1960-1961 (Box-folder 17:9)
    - Correspondence City of Montgomery Reports 1960 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - Executive Comm. Correspondence January, 1961 (Box-folder 17:11)
    - Correspondence February, 1961 (Box-folder 17:12)
    - Correspondence The Intercollegian March 1-23, 1961 (Box-folder 17:13)
    - The Alabama Democrat March 24-31, 1961 (Box-folder 17:14)
    - Correspondence April, 1961 (Box-folder 17a:1)
    - Correspondence May-November, 1961 (Box-folder 17a:2)
    - Correspondence 1062-1966 (Box-folder 17a:3)
    - Sociology Section June 9, 1962 (Box-folder 17a:4)
    - Sociology Section November-December, 1962 (Box-folder 17a:5)
    - Sociology Section October 1-11, 1962 (Box-folder 17a:6)
    - Sociology Section October 12-30, 1962 (Box-folder 17a:7)
    - Sociology Section January-March, 1963 (Box-folder 17a:8)
    - Sociology Section April 2-9, 1963 (Box-folder 17a:9)
    - Sociology Section April 10-27, 1963 (Box-folder 17a:10)
  - The Virginia Social Science Association 1964-1967
    - V.S.S.A Membership Roster (Box-folder 18:1)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence November-December 1959 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence January-February, 1960 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence March-April, 1960 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence May, 1960 (Box-folder 18:5)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence April-August, 1964 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence September-October, 1964 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence January-February, 1965 (Box-folder 18:8)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence March-April, 1965 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence May-June, 1965 (Box-folder 18:10)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence September-December, 1965 (Box-folder 18:11)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence January-April, 1966 (Box-folder 18:12)
    - V.S.S.A. Correspondence January-April, 1967 (Box-folder 18:13)
    - A.S.S.T. Business Meeting (Minutes) May 7, 1955 (Box-folder 18a:1)
    - A.S.S.T. Annual Report September 1955 (Box-folder 18a:2)
    - A.S.S.T. Annual Report May 1956 (Box-folder 18a:3)
    - A.S.S.T. Annual Report May 2, 1957 (Box-folder 18a:4)
    - A.S.S.T. Annual Report March 1961 (Box-folder 18a:5)
    - A.S.S.T. Membership 1956 (Box-folder 18a:6)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1939 (Box-folder 18a:7)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1940 (Box-folder 18a:8)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1941 (Box-folder 18a:9)
    - A.S.S.T. Program- 8th Conference May 1, 1943 (Box-folder 18a:9a)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1944 (Box-folder 18a:10)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1945 (Box-folder 18a:11)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1946 (Box-folder 18a:12)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1948 (Box-folder 18a:13)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1955 (Box-folder 18a:14)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1956 (Box-folder 18a:15)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1957 (Box-folder 18a:16)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1958 (Box-folder 18a:17)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1960 (Box-folder 18a:18)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1961 (Box-folder 18a:19)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1962 (Box-folder 18a:20)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1965 (Box-folder 18a:21)
    - A.S.S.T. Program 1968 (Box-folder 18a:22)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1944 (Box-folder 18a:23)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1945 (Box-folder 18a:24)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1946 (Box-folder 18a:25)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1955 (Box-folder 18a:26)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1956 (Box-folder 18a:27)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1957 (Box-folder 18a:28)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1958 (Box-folder 18a:29)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1959 (Box-folder 18a:30)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1959 (Box-folder 18a:31)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1960 (Box-folder 18a:32)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1962 (Box-folder 18a:33)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1963 (Box-folder 18a:34)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1964 (Box-folder 18a:35)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1965 (Box-folder 18a:36)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1966 (Box-folder 18a:37)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1967 (Box-folder 18a:38)
    - A.S.S.T. Newsletter 1968 (Box-folder 18a:39)
    - Virginia Social Science Association Program 1956, 1958 (Box-folder 18a:40)
    - Program, The Virginia Conference of College Science Teachers March 13- April 1, 1939 (Box-folder 18a:41)
  - Virginia Council of Churches
    - Virginia Council of Churches Minutes 1952 (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Minutes 1953-1955 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Minutes 1957 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Minutes 1958 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Report: On Stronger Rural Churches January 4, 1952 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Report: Interracial Committee 1952 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Reports: Church Conditions 1952 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Reports 1957 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Reports 1958 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Reports 1957-1959 (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Reports (Constitution and by laws) (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Reports 1943-1954 (Box-folder 19:12)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 19:14)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 19:15)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1952-1954 (Box-folder 19:16)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 19:17)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 19:18)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 19:19)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 19:20)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder 19:21)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder 19:22)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 19:23)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box-folder 19:24)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Programs (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Printed (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Printed (Box-folder 20:3)
  - The Faculty Christian Fellowship (F.C.F)
    - F.C.F. 1952 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - F.C.F.-Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - F.C.F.-Correspondence 1958-1959 (Box-folder 20:6)
    - F.C.F.-Correspondence 1960-1962 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - F.C.F.-Correspondence 1963 (Box-folder 20:8)
    - F.C.F.-Correspondence 1964 (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Hollins College
    - Hollins College-Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Hollins College-Correspondence 1963 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Hollins College-Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Hollins College-Correspondence 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20:13)
  - Central State Hospitial
    - Central State Hospital Newsletters 1961-1962 (Box-folder 20:14)
    - Central State Hospital Newsletters 1963 (Box-folder 20:15)
  - The Society of Social Problem
    - Reports SSSP 1956 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1951-1952 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1952 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - SSSP-Correspondence January-June, 1953 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - SSSP-Correspondence July-December, 1953 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - SSSP-Correspondence January-July, 1957 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - SSSP-Correspondence August-September, 1957 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - SSSP-Correspondence October-December, 1957 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - SSSP-Correspondence January-July, 1959 (Box-folder 21:14)
    - SSSP-Correspondence August-December, 1959 (Box-folder 21:15)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder 22:1)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder 22:2)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 22:3)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1963 (Box-folder 22:4)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1964 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - SSSP-Correspondence 1965-1967; n.d. (Box-folder 22:6)
    - SSSP-Printed March, 1958 (Box-folder 22:7)
  - The Southern Sociology Society
    - SSS-Correspondence 1939-1944 (Box-folder 22:8)
    - SSS-Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 22:9)
    - SSS-Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 22:10)
    - SSS-Correspondence 1960-1964 (Box-folder 22:11)
  - The Frontiers Club
    - Frontiers Club Minutes 1957 (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Frontiers Club Minutes 1957 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Proposal (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Proposal- The Family Life Conference 1957 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Correspondence-Chesson 1957 (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Correspondence- Frontier Natural 1958-1960 (Box-folder 23:6)
    - List of Officers 1957 (Box-folder 23:7)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club 1951-1955 (Box-folder 23:8)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club January-May, 1956 (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club June-December, 1956 (Box-folder 23:10)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club January-June, 1957 (Box-folder 23:11)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club July-August, 1954 (Box-folder 23:12)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club September, 1957 (Box-folder 23:13)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club October 1-15, 1957 (Box-folder 23:14)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club October 21-31, 1975 (Box-folder 23:15)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club November, 1957 (Box-folder 23:16)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club December, 1957 (Box-folder 23:17)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club January 1-14, 1958 (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club January 15-20, 1958 (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Correspondence-Frontiers Club January 21-31, 1958 (Box-folder 24:3)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club February 1-10, 1958 (Box-folder 24:4)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club February 11-15, 1958 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club February 17-18, 1958 (Box-folder 24:6)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club February 19-20, 1958 (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club February 21-28, 1958 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club March 1-13, 1958 (Box-folder 24:9)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club March 14, 1958 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club March 17-31, 1958 (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club March 17-19, 1958 (Box-folder 25:1)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club March 21, 1958 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club March 22-29, 1958 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club April 1-14, 1958 (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club April 16-30, 1958 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club May 1-28, 1958 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club June 2-29, 1958 (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club August-November, 1958 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club (Box-folder 25:11)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Conference Correspondence-Frontiers Club (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Frontiers Newsletter (2) February, 1956 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter June, 1956 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter (3) February, 1957 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter July, 1957 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter October, 1957 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter (2) April, 1958 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter (2) July, 1958 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter July, 1959 (Box 25a)
    - Frontiers Newsletter October, 1958- February, 1959 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontier May, 1954 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontier September, 1954 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontier October, 1954 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontier December, 1954 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman July, 1952 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman December, 1952 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman April, 1955 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman January, 1959 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman May, 1963 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman February, 1965 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman Spring, 1966 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman Summer, 1966 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman Fall, 1966 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman Fall, 1965-Winter, 1966 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman 1st quarter 1968 (Box 25a)
    - The Frontiersman (Box 25a)
    - Printed-Miscellaneous (Box-folder 25a:1)
  - The Rural Sociology Society
    - RSS Correspondence 1939, 1948 (Box-folder 26:1)
    - RSS Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box-folder 26:2)
    - RSS Correspondence July, 1962 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - RSS Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - RSS Correspondence 1965 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - RSS Correspondence 1966 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - The Southern Regional Educational Board
    - Conference Meeting March 1-2, 1956 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Advisory Committee March 14, 1958 (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Conference Meeting July 17-18, 1958 (Box-folder 26:9)
    - Mental Health July 18, 1958 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Research July 18, 1958 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - Nuclear Energy July 18, 1958 (Box-folder 26:12)
    - Relationships July 18, 1958 (Box-folder 26:13)
    - Advisory Committiee December 1, 1958 (Box-folder 26:14)
  - Virginia Council of Human Relations
    - VA. CHR Reports 1962-1965 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - VA. CHR Board Meetings and Minutes 1961-1962 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - VA. CHR Board Meetings and Minutes 1963 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - VA. CHR Board Meeting and Minutes 1964 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - VA. CHR Board Meetings and Minutes 1965 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 27:8)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 27:10)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence January-October, 1963 (Box-folder 27:11)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence November-December, 1963 (Box-folder 27:12)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1964 (Box-folder 27:13)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1965 (Box-folder 27:14)
    - VA. CHR Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box-folder 27:15)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity
    - Committee on Education, Reports 1941-1942 (Box-folder 28:1)
    - ommittiee on Education, Reports 1956-1958 (Box-folder 28:2)
    - Education of Citizenship, Correspondence 1931-1935 (Box-folder 28:3)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1940 (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 28:5)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1943 (Box-folder 28:7)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 28:8)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 28:9)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 28:10)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 28:11)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 28:12)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 28:13)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence January-June, 1950 (Box-folder 28:14)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence November-December, 1950 (Box-folder 28:15)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence January-May, 1951 (Box-folder 28:16)
    - Committiee on Education, Correspondence June, 1951 (Box-folder 28:17)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence April-May, 1952 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence January-May, 1953 (Box-folder 29:2)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence March-April, 1953 (Box-folder 29:3)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence July-August, 1953 (Box-folder 29:4)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence January-April, 1954 (Box-folder 29:5)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence May-November, 1954 (Box-folder 29:6)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence January-March, 1956 (Box-folder 29:8)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence April, 1956 (Box-folder 29:9)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence May-June, 1956 (Box-folder 29:10)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence October-December, 1956 (Box-folder 29:11)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 29:12)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 29:13)
    - Committee on Education, Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 29:14)
    - "Why the Negro in Virginia Should Vote" 1940 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - "How Using Our Rights to Vote can Contribute to National Defense" 1942 (Box-folder 30:2)
    - "What Should Negroes do now to Ensure Their Rights as Citizens After the War" 1943 (Box-folder 30:3)
    - "why Should I Want to Vote in the Coming Presidential Election" 1944 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - "What can High School Students do to Build a Better World" 1945 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - "The Education We Need in the Post War World" 1946 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - "How can High Schools Students Contribute Toward Our Advancement of Civil Rights?" 1948 (Box-folder 30:7)
    - "Why be Concerned About Civil Rights & the History of My High School" 1949 (Box-folder 30:8)
    - "How does Voting Affect the Welfare of Citizens in a Community (City, State, Nation)" 1950 (Box-folder 30:9)
    - "The Effect of War on Our Educational Intitutions" 1951 (Box-folder 30:10)
    - "Should the Virginia Compulsory School Attendance Law be Changed to Promote Pupils to Discontinue School Upon Completion of the Elementary Grades" 1952 (Box-folder 30:11)
    - "Education for Citizenship Should Racial Segregation be Abolished in Virginia's Public Schools?" 1953 (Box-folder 30:12)
    - "How Should Segregation be Abolished in Public Transportation and Public Schools"? 1954 (Box-folder 30:13)
    - "How May the Public Schools in My Country (or City) be Integrated" 1955 (Box-folder 30:14)
    - "Minority Group Responsiblities in Achieving an Integrated Society" 1956 (Box-folder 30:15)
    - Essay (Box-folder 30:16)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Photos statewide essay contest (Box-folder 30:17)
    - Minutes (Box-folder 31:1)